



(+852) 6040 8671



shirau@gmail.com



sasconcept.ftp.cc

EDUCATION

2006-2008

Multimedia Design & Technology (HD)

Hong Kong Polytechnic University

1999-2006

Secondary 1 - 7 Munsang College (Hong Kong Island)

SKILLS

User Experience

- Persona
- Target Audience Journey
- Information Architecture
- Site Mapping
- Wireframe
- User Flows
- Prototyping
- Quality Assurance
- Usability Testing
- Collaboration with Development Teams

Visual Design

- Mood Board
- Branding
- Interface Design
- Information Design

SHIRLEYAU UX & UI DESIGNER

DIGITAL PRODUCTS, PRINT PRODUCTS

SUMMARY

A seasoned digital product designer with 9 years of experience designing products across various sectors including retail, education, gaming, bank and digital advertisement business. Proficient in user-centered design processes, specializing in rapid prototyping, interaction design and final user interface visual design. Looking to excel in both analytical and creative thinking, and shape better user experience design.

EXPERIENCE

9.2014 - Present

Advisory Senior UX Designer iClick Interactive Asia Limited



B2B Data Analysis Platform, Ad Targeting Platform, Wechat Mini Program, Mobile Ad Landing Webpages

- Conduct ongoing research of web-based user interface development best practices
- Build and design prototypes of proposed features in company products
- Come up with user-centered design solutions with teams in Shanghai and Beijing such as project managers and engineers to understand user needs and business requirements
- Collorate with Ctrip on delivering Wechat mini programs to reach out China market
- Online advertisment support: Banner and mobile ad landing page design

1.2014 - 6.2014

UI & UX Designer nBition Development Limited



Mobile Game Apps, Marketing Materials

- Work closely with the team to design user interfaces of mobile priorie applications (games & apps) and reponsive websites. Deliverables included research, interaction flow, wireframes, prototype and final visual design
- Handling projects from concept to production with project manager and developers
- App review and provide recommendations after launching apps to the marketplace

5.2013 - 12.2013

Multimedia Designer Justsolve Consulting Limited



Andriod Mobile Game Apps, Responsive Web Interface

- Lead designer and work closely with engineers from conceptualization to final visual design
- · Directly communicate and organise work milestone with client
- Deliverables included online & offline products: mobile applications user interfaces, flash animation, promotional materials (prints)

6.2012 - 5.2013

Multimedia Designer Multimedia Global Limited



Showcase (Kiosk) Interface, Web Interface

- Work closely with designers, programmers and project managers on mobile phone applications and digital showcases (Kiosk) interfaces, websites and offline marketing materials
- Various client projects including Hang Seng Bank, Sands Macau, Joint Publishing HK...etc

8.2009 - 6.2012

Senior Graphic Designer Fingerprint Limited

FINGERPRINT

Graphic, Branding, Printing, Exhibition Material

- Print design and web design for marketing and branding services
- Produced artwork for client in-store decoration
- Communicate and organize the output process and timetable with clients
- Completing tasks by collaborating with junior colleagues

5.2008 - 7.2009

Graphic Designer Suncolor Limited



Graphic, Branding, Print Design Products

- Print design and web design for marketing and branding services.
- Printing composing and directly deal with clients' technical output problems

INTERNSHIP

10.2007 - 12.2007

Web Designer

Big Fish Design Limited

12.2006 - 2.2008

Student Assistant - Design

Hong Kong Polytechnic University

TOOLS

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- · Adobe After Effect
- Adobe Animate (Flash)
- Adobe XD
- Sketch App
- UXPIN
- Axure RP9
- Invision

LANGUAGES

Cantonese

Mother Language

English

Basic Speaking Fluent Writing

Mandarin

<u>F</u>luent